## **Callum Jake Thompson | Software Developer**

Location: 59 Regency Court, Rushden, Northamptonshire, NN10 6EY

Telephone: 07999 314884

Email: cal8thompson@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

I am a software developer learning Python, Java and C++, alongside front-end web development such as HTML5, JavaScript and CSS. I am keen in expressing my ideas with other passionate employees, learning from them and building my knowledge in software development.

#### **Education & Qualifications**

Walton High School (2016 - 2020)

- English Language Grade 4
- \* English Literature Grade 5
- ❖ Science (Combined) Grade 4-4
- \* Media Studies Distinction
- Media Studies Report Distinction
- Computer Science Grade 7
- Business Studies Grade 5
- History Grade 4
- Mathematics Grade 5

Milton Keynes College (2020 - 2021)

Digital Technologies Level 3

BTEC National Extended Certificate in Information Technology

## **Career Summary**

10/11/2020 - 02/02/2021

ix47, Milton Keynes

**Software Developer - Work Placement** 

Worked on a car dealership program in Java with other students participating within the work placement.

- Learnt fundamentals and basics of Java and Object-Oriented-Programming
- Introduced to structure of low level languages
- Understanding of the workplace in the face of a professional software developer

03/2019 - 09/2019

MK Scouts, Milton Keynes

**Volunteer Young Leader For Beavers** 

Looked after small groups of children, helping them with work and activities.

- Leadership skills
- Assisting groups of children without assistance
- Confidence in talking to other leaders

# 01/2019 – Ongoing Cyberstart: HM Government's Cyber Security Program Participant

Make programs, inspect source code of websites and find the solutions to the problems presented.

- Develop out-of-box thinking
- Learn, develop and execute programs to decipher scrambled data using Python
- Solve professional cyber dilemmas handled by experienced cyber security experts

### Core Skills & Achievements

- Detail Orientated
- Logical Thinking
- Data Driven
- Analytical
- Complex Problem Solver
- Self-Starter
- Basic Programming Skills (Python, C++ and Java)
- MS Office (Word, Excel, Access and Powerpoint).
- Duke of Edinburgh (Silver and Bronze)
- Walton High School Council Representative
- Walton High School Prefect